<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>santerre.xyz</title>
    <link>https://santerre.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on santerre.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 20:26:04 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://santerre.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://santerre.xyz/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 20:26:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://santerre.xyz/posts/intro/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://santerre.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://santerre.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>General Originally from the east coast of Canada, I have lived in Toronto for most of my life for school and the first three years of my career, I am currently living in Tokyo with my partner as we both enjoy travelling surrounding Asian countries!
Some of my hobbies include:
 Cycling &amp;amp; Bike Packing (feel free to add me on Strava) Reading (see here for more info on what I&amp;rsquo;m reading) Travelling (see my gallery for some photos from my various trips, WIP) Gaming (see my steam for what I&amp;rsquo;m currently playing)  Career Starting off as an Electrical Engineering Major at the University of Toronto, I originally was planning to pursue a career in the field of Telecom Hardware, but later I pivoted to Software as I fell in love with developing network and cloud applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://santerre.xyz/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://santerre.xyz/projects/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of the projects that I have worked on/am working on that
GigK8s Kubernetes system to auction/offer your spare Kubernetes compute to the market.
Triggers Automation system to map incoming webhooks from any source (Slack, Github, etc&amp;hellip;) to predefined workflows that transform your data to other input sources (Slack, Github, etc&amp;hellip;). Created out of lack of a bridge for Slack webhooks to trigger GH Actions.
Gossip-rs A reimplementation of the memberlist library written in Rust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What am I currently Reading</title>
      <link>https://santerre.xyz/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://santerre.xyz/books/</guid>
      <description>Fiction Tiamat&amp;rsquo;s Wrath (James S.A. Corey)
Having been a huge fan of The Expanse series since it first came out, I finally had a chance to get a copy of this book over here in Japan.
Non-Fiction The Wars of Afghanistan (Peter Tompsen)
Fascinating book looking into the history of the middle east and how it contributed to the events of our modern society.
Technical/Software Accelerate (Nicole Forsgren, Jez Humble, Gene Kim)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>